Mohammad AL Salamat

+60 178464650 Alomda.alslmat@gmail.com

Junior Web Developer specializing in front-end and back-end development. I have a good knowledge of all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including {HTML5, PHP, JavaScript , JQuery , CSS, Sass , MySQL, Oracle ,Veu.js ,Laravel Framework ,and python }



Experience

• Web Developer - 02/2020 to 08/2020 George HealthCare, Malaysia

It is Internship period but I got lots of experiences where I built the main admin page for the company's website and I helped them to improve lots of features to make the website more attractive to users and helped the team to build the security for the website then worked on Front-End side where I helped to build the functions to get the data from the database.

• Web Developer - 02/2019 to 09/2019 Final year Project, IIUM, Malaysia

Final year project (FYP) is one of the biggest challenges that I had due the tools that I used to build the website where I used Codelgniter Framework to complete it in very short time, and it was my first own website using new tools such as Codelgniter,

• Web Developer - 02/2018 to 01/2019

Free Lancer, IIUM

Building websites for the users who ask me to do so such as Student's Final year. Besides tens of other individual projects One of my works was an E-commerce website to sell Suits.

SKILLS & Certifications

- PHP Frameworks : Codelgniter, Laravel.
- Building Database Applications in PHP
- Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4
- HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Web Developers
- Advanced Styling with Responsive Design

Skill Highlights

- programming skills
- ✓ good problem solver
- ✓ Project management
- ✓ Service-focused

Education

Bachelor's in information and Communication Technology, International Islamic University Malaysia (IIUM), KL, Malaysia

September 2016 - January 2020

Languages

✓ Arabic : C-2

✓ English: B-2

✓ Malay : A-1

REFERENCE

Ali A.Alwan Aljuboori

Assistant Professor

KULLIYYAH OF INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY International

Islamic University Malaysia aliamer@iium.edu.m